<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>self-development on Hi, it&#39;s me, Lu</title>
    <link>https://techsavvy.cc/categories/self-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in self-development on Hi, it&#39;s me, Lu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://techsavvy.cc/categories/self-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM SkillsBuild PowerBI program </title>
      <link>https://techsavvy.cc/projects/ibm_bi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techsavvy.cc/projects/ibm_bi/</guid>
      <description>IBM SkillsBuild PowerBI program is a certification program offered by IBM in collaboration with Udemy and SkillsBuild.
The 8-weeks program consists of a series of courses covering various parts of reports in PowerBI:
 Microsoft Power BI - Power BI Desktop Course(24h) People Analytics with Power BI (5h) Supply chain (2.5h) Final Project (20h)  Apart from being a completely new subject for me, I also faced the additional challenge of taking the course entirely in Spanish as part of the Datahack scholarship program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suntan telegram bot</title>
      <link>https://techsavvy.cc/projects/suntanbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techsavvy.cc/projects/suntanbot/</guid>
      <description>Overview In the past, I came across an article discussing the &amp;ldquo;Goltis1 Scheme&amp;rdquo;, a method to achieve a quicker suntan without experiencing sunburns. Over time, I often thought about how beneficial it would be to have more than just an image of this scheme. An interactive application or similar tool would enhance the experience and make it easier to understand and apply the technique effectively.
1also known as Vladimir Vuksta</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Epam Trainee</title>
      <link>https://techsavvy.cc/projects/java_epam_trainee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techsavvy.cc/projects/java_epam_trainee/</guid>
      <description>Overview  Epam Java University External Course prepares individuals for a new career in IT and includes the following modules:
 Basics of Computer Science Version Control with Git Java Core + Collections and Streams Design  Databases Web Programming Basics Testing Spring Framework Final Project   Final Project Fot the final project I chose Payment varian. https://github.com/lublyanka/epam_final_task
In this project, I have successfully implemented a simplified account-payment system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum management</title>
      <link>https://techsavvy.cc/projects/scrum_pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techsavvy.cc/projects/scrum_pm/</guid>
      <description>Scrum Management can be compared to a cockatoo due to its vibrant and dynamic nature, mirroring the characteristics of this colorful bird.
High Energy and Enthusiasm: Just like a cockatoo&amp;rsquo;s energetic and enthusiastic demeanor, Scrum Management is known for its high energy and enthusiasm. Scrum teams are motivated and committed to delivering value in each sprint, fostering a positive and vibrant work atmosphere.
Intelligent and Adaptive: Cockatoos are highly intelligent birds known for their problem-solving abilities and adaptability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Project Management Professional Program</title>
      <link>https://techsavvy.cc/projects/coursera_pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techsavvy.cc/projects/coursera_pm/</guid>
      <description>Google Professional Certificate Project Management is a certification program offered by Google in collaboration with Coursera.
The program consists of a series of six courses covering various topics such as project initiation, planning, execution, monitoring and controlling, and closing.
It takes on average 6 months to complete with a workload of 15 hours per week and is designed for individuals with varying levels of project management experience, including those who are experienced professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google IT Support Professional Program</title>
      <link>https://techsavvy.cc/projects/coursera_it_support/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techsavvy.cc/projects/coursera_it_support/</guid>
      <description>Google Professional Certificate IT Support Management is a certification program offered by Google in collaboration with Coursera.
The program consists of a series of five courses covering various topics such as computer systems, networking, operating systems, system administration, and security. The program is delivered online and .
It takes on average 5 months to complete with a workload of 10 hours per week and is designed for individuals who wants to improve their existing knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultrarev Project Management Internship</title>
      <link>https://techsavvy.cc/projects/ultrarev_pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techsavvy.cc/projects/ultrarev_pm/</guid>
      <description>RadicalX is a Virtual Internship Platform that helps aspiring professionals to discover their dream career by gaining experience from industry job simulations that replicate work at top tech companies.
The program helped me to strengthen my skills, mindset, and network to be a high-impact team member at innovative companies.
 Artifacts Communication Plan Ultrarev Butter Onboarding  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISTQB Foundational Level</title>
      <link>https://techsavvy.cc/projects/istqb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://techsavvy.cc/projects/istqb/</guid>
      <description>The ISTQB Certificate is a globally recognized professional certification program designed to validate software testing expertise and proficiency. Developed by the International Software Testing Qualifications Board, this certification provides individuals with a comprehensive understanding of software testing principles, techniques, and best practices.
 Artifacts  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>